Rajesh Kumar

(Full Stack Web developer) I am having 6+ monts of UI experience and backend services. I have good experienc for making the application aligned with MERN. I have ability to learn new technologies guickly and good debugging skills.



- rajeshatka4746@gmail.com
- Bagodar ,Giridih, Jharkhand, India
- github.com/rajeshkumar5295

- +91 62060 98820
- in linkedin.com/in/rajesh-kumar-72a573254

EDUCATION

B.Tech in Computer Science & Engineering

Ramgarh Engineering College, Ramgarh (Jharkhand)

2020 - 2024 8.4 cgpa

Intermediate of Science (I. Sc.)

St. Columba's college, Hazaribagh (JAC Board, Ranchi)

2017 - 2019 79%

Matriculation(10th board)

High school Atka (JAC Board, Ranchi)

2017 90%

WORK EXPERIENCE

Stencii (Web Developer Intern)

Noctilucent Technologies LLP

10/2023 - 12/2023

Technologies used: ReactJs, javaScript, Tailwind css, Bootstrap, AWS, MongoDb, ExpressJs, NodeJs

Responsibilities:

- Stencii creates fantastically easy-to-use online graphic design tools and templates.
- Gathering requirements from clients.
- In Backend creating APIs, Modals and Controller functions
- In Fronted integrateing APIs, designing pages and debugging

Web Developer Intern

Intern Crowd

10/2022 - 11/2022

Technologies used: HTML, CSS, javaScript, Tailwind css, Bootstrap, MongoDb,ExpressJs, NodeJs, ReactJs

Responsibilities:

- Created demo app end to end which is used acroos the floor.
- In Fronted integrateing APIs, designing pages and debugging
- In Backend creating APIs, Modals and Controller functions

INTERESTS

Music ,Photography

SKILLS



PERSONAL PROJECTS

Shopping App

- https://mvc-ecommerce.vercel.app/
- Technologies used: ReactJs, ExpressJs, MongoDb, NodeJs, Context API, Bootstrap, React Icons, JWT Authentication and packages like bcrypt js for hashing the password

Blood Bank App

- https://mern-blood-bank-app-one.vercel.app/login
- It is a role base project, having role like Admin, Donar, Hospital, Organisation. Created Using MERN and Redux

Ecommerce app

- https://ecomm-mallu.netlify.app/
- Created with React js, firebase, Tailwind Css and Redux

Amazon clone

- https://fir-project-e7c14.web.app/
- Created with React Js, firebase, Redux, Tailwind css

CERTIFICATES

Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp with MERN Stack Projects

By Udemy (<code>https://udemy-certificate.s3.amazonaws.com/image/UC-3f72fed9-a36d-47b0-9e77-7962377eb897.jpg?v=1687935921000</code>)

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

3

Full Professional Proficiency

C ++

Full Professional Proficiency

JAVA

Professional Working Proficiency